Next Episode.
I don't usually talk that crazy.
Is it everyone? Do you like Momota's Instagram posts?
It's embarrassing if I do it every time.
I'm sure the people I follow will see it.
Every third time, every third time, every third time.
I want to press them all.
I'm just feeling, you know, wow, you're so cute.
I'm thinking about it in my heart.
The other day at the Folk Village, we were all getting along so well...
I grabbed her.
I grabbed her in a hug, and I think my body moved before I thought about it.
Oh, you physically grabbed me!
I thought that's what it means when your body moves on its own
Oh, cool!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha.
Can I ask you to come in?
Yes, please.
I'm so nervous.
Can I have some water?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, my God. Breathe.
Breathe. Just breathe.
Just breathe, please.
Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
I know this is a nerve-wracking time for you.
When you're in trouble.
Yeah, I know.
When you first told me about this,
I'm sorry? Me? I was like, "Me?
But I was really worried at first,
I was so worried that I had a hard time breathing,
But as we talked, I felt the warmth of Kanako-chan,But as we talked, I got used to Kanako's warmth,
I was able to get used to your warmth and the sense that you made me feel very calm,
I felt very calm, too, and I was happy to be able to talk with you about many things.
What did you want to talk about?
When asked again what I wanted to talk about...,
I don't really have anything to say,
What is it?
There are so many things I want to talk about,
But when I'm asked again what I want to talk about,
I don't know what I want to talk about,
But, I have a lot of things to talk about, like how we spend our time at home,
I was very happy to know that we had so much in common,
I was happy just to be in the same space with them.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
That's right. This was the first time for us to have such a one-on-one talk.
Wow.
But you always try so hard, Mitachan,
I have the impression that you are always trying your best, and you are very considerate to everyone you talk to,
I don't think my impression of her has changed in any way.
But I have learned that we have a lot in common, or rather, we have a lot of similarities,
I am a little worried about your future. I am worried about your future.
I know that I don't go out this much either,
I wonder if you will be okay? I wonder if you will be okay.
But I'm sure she'll be fine. I'm sure.
I hope you will be able to move forward in your own way from now on.
I hope you will be able to move forward in your own way. This time, I had a chance to talk with Eve Eve about many things.
It's not often that I get a chance to talk about my younger colleagues,
I was very happy to have this opportunity today.
I was very happy to have this opportunity to talk with her today,
I think I was able to do that today,
I also hope to fulfill my promise to go out to dinner privately with you soon,
I hope to fulfill my promise to have dinner with her privately soon, so I'll let you all know when that happens.
So, thank you very much for your time today.
I'm just going to let my mind move on.
I guess so.Oh, yeah.
Oh, so much.
Cute.
Give me a different pattern.
What is it? I don't know.
It could be something like this.
Yes, I think it's this one. 12345 Yes. You sure you don't want me to double-label it?
I didn't say that.
I can't look at the wrong eyes.
I hate it when people look at me. I hate it when people look at me.
I don't like to be seen. I don't like to be seen.
I want to look at them, but I can't.
I'd like to, but Tyche...
I want to be seen, but I can't be seen.
I'm not supposed to smile when I'm being watched.
Can I be serious for a second? Let's lick each other's lips.
Wow, that was fast!
That's new.
Let's have a lick.
Come closer, let's get a closer look.
Okay, here we go.
Don't run away.
Let's have a lickety-split.
If you laugh, you lose.
What? One more time?
It hasn't started.
Okay.
Let's play lickety-split.
Laugh and you lose.
Up!
Good night.
It's already a crushing defeat. Overwhelmed.
I don't want to.
Touch it. Spider.Touch it. Touch the spider.
Touch it.
Why?
I don't want to.
Thank you very much.
You did it.
Thank you.
I don't know what to do.
Now, Mita-chan.
It's Mita-chan.
You always talk to me afterwards, you know.
She always has a lot to say to me.
Nervous.
Hands are cold.
My feet hurt, but my hands are cold.
I understand. I understand.
I get it. I have years ahead of me.
You can't have bad nerves.
It's going to happen.
Do you get nervous a lot?
Yes, I am.
I understand.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
See you.
Also.
Thanks for your hard work.
Take care.
Thank you very much.
You're surprised.